 {
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "question": "What is the point of assembly (POA) for new students?",
        "answer": "All new students are required to attend the Point of Assembly (POA) for registration before entering the assigned residential college. The POA locations are:\n- Padang Kawad Palapes: KK1, KK2, KK3, KK4, KK7, KK8, KK10, KK12\n- Kolej Kediaman Tun Syed Zahiruddin (KK9): KK9"
      },
      {
        "question": "What documents are required for registration?",
        "answer": "You need to bring the following documents for registration:\n1. A copy of the offer letter.\n2. Completed Residential College Registration Form & Letter of Undertaking (LOU).\n3. A passport-sized photo with a blue background taken professionally (selfies are not allowed)."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the registration dates and times?",
        "answer": "The registration dates and times are as follows:\n\n**Padang Kawad Palapes and Kolej Kediaman Tun Syed Zahiruddin (KK9)**:\n1. **30 September 2023 (Saturday)**:\n- 9:00 AM – 1:00 PM: KK2, KK12 (Female only), KK9 (Female only)\n- 2:00 PM – 5:00 PM: KK1, KK12 (Male only), KK9 (Female only)\n\n2. **1 October 2023 (Sunday)**:\n- 9:00 AM – 1:00 PM: KK8, KK10, KK9 (Male only)\n- 2:00 PM – 5:00 PM: KK3, KK4, KK7, KK9 (Male only)"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the registration process at Padang Kawad Palapes?",
        "answer": "The registration process at Padang Kawad Palapes is as follows:\n1. Parents/Guardians enter the POA area and follow staff guidance to park their vehicle.\n2. Students register at the registration tent. Parents/Guardians place the student's personal items in the designated luggage area at the registration tent.\n3. After registration, students should load personal items onto the shuttle bus with the help of staff.\n4. Only students will proceed to the assigned residential college using the provided shuttle bus.\n5. Parents/Guardians must leave the campus once the student has boarded the shuttle bus. They are not allowed to be at the residential college area throughout the registration day."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the registration process at Kolej Kediaman Tun Syed Zahiruddin (KK9)?",
        "answer": "The registration process at Kolej Kediaman Tun Syed Zahiruddin (KK9) is as follows:\n1. Only one vehicle per family is allowed into the POA. Registration is conducted via a drive-in system, with staff guiding the vehicle parking.\n2. Students and parents/guardians have 10 minutes to place the student’s personal items in the designated luggage tent.\n3. Students proceed to the registration area in the Administration Block. Parents/Guardians must leave the POA after unloading the student’s belongings to make way for other vehicles. They are not allowed in the residential college area throughout the registration day."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the registration process at the Tun Syed Zahruddin Residential College (KK9)?",
        "answer": "The registration process at the Tun Syed Zahruddin Residential College (KK9) involves only one parent/guardian vehicle allowed to enter the POA area, drive-in registration, unloading student's personal belongings, and proceeding to the registration area at the Administration Block."
      },
      {
        "question": "What personal items should students bring for UM-WOW?",
        "answer": "Students should prepare personal necessities such as study equipment, pillows, pillowcases, bed sheets, sports shoes and attire, formal wear, national dress, prayer essentials, personal hygiene items, etc. Students are encouraged to make cashless transactions and avoid carrying large amounts of cash to prevent loss."
      },
      {
        "question": "Can new students bring vehicles to the campus?",
        "answer": "New students are NOT ALLOWED to bring vehicles to the campus. UM provides transportation facilities at Terminal 1 and Terminal 2 KLIA to pick up students from Sabah and Sarawak on the registration day and two days prior. More details are available on the official link."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the UM-WOW program?",
        "answer": "All new students must participate in the UM-WOW MHS program starting from the registration date. Personal matters should be handled before or after the UM-WOW MHS program"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the dress code for UM-WOW?",
        "answer": "During UM-WOW MHS, all new students must dress neatly and appropriately according to Malaysian norms and culture. The dress code for male students includes a collared T-shirt, dark-colored long pants, sports/closed shoes, and traditional attire. Female students should wear a collared T-shirt, dark-colored long pants/long skirt, sports/closed shoes, traditional attire, and Baju Kurung."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can parents/guardians contact the UM-WOW MHS Secretariat?",
        "answer": "Parents/guardians can contact the UM-WOW MHS Secretariat at the Student Affairs Department, Universiti Malaya, via telephone at 03-7967 3507 / 3577 / 7795 or email at umwow@um.edu.my / hep@um.edu.my."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where can I find more information about UM-WOW?",
        "answer": "For further information, you can contact the UM-WOW MHS Secretariat at the Department of Student Affairs, University of Malaya. You can reach them via phone at 03-7967 3507 / 3577 / 7795 or email at umwow@um.edu.my / hep@um.edu.my. Additionally, you can visit the official website: [UM-WOW MHS Special Activities](https://hep.um.edu.my/special-activities)."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the date of the Week of Welcome?",
        "answer": "The Week of Welcome (WOW) will take place from 30 September 2023 to 5 October 2023."
      },
      {
        "question": "Can I skip the Week of Welcome?",
        "answer": "It is highly recommended for all new students to attend the Week of Welcome as it includes important orientation sessions, registration, and activities designed to help you settle into university life. If you have specific concerns, you may contact the Student Affairs Department for more information."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the activities scheduled for 30 September 2023?",
        "answer": "The activities for 30 September 2023 (Saturday) include: 9:00 AM - 10:00 AM: Registration 10:00 AM - 11:00 AM: Distribution of MHS Kit 11:00 AM - 12:30 PM: Session with Residential College (RC) Management [Location: Residential Colleges] 12:30 PM - 2:30 PM: Program Pengenalan Asas Kesedaran Mengundi Kepada Pelajar Baharu Institusi Pendidikan Tinggi (IPT) [Location: Dewan Tunku Canselor] 2:30 PM - 3:30 PM: Student Carnival Activities [Location: Residential College] 3:30 PM - 4:00 PM: Break Time 4:00 PM - 5:00 PM: Closing Ceremony UM-WOW:MHS 2023/2024 [Location: UM Arena] 5:30 PM - 7:00 PM: Session with Pemudahcara Mahasiswa (PM) [Location: Residential Colleges] 7:00 PM - 8:00 PM: Residential Colleges' Activities 8:30 PM - 9:30 PM: Residential Colleges' Activities 9:30 PM - 10:30 PM: Residential Colleges' Activities 10:30 PM - 11:30 PM: Residential Colleges' Activities"
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the activities scheduled for 1 October 2023?",
        "answer": "The activities for 1 October 2023 (Sunday) include: 9:00 AM - 10:00 AM: Opening Ceremony and New Students Pledge by Dato' Vice-Chancellor [Location: Dewan Tunku Canselor] 10:00 AM - 11:00 AM: Break Time 11:00 AM - 12:30 PM: Session with UM Clinic, Bursar, Library, Security Department, OSHREC, Counselling and Disability Empowerment Division [Location: Dewan Tunku Canselor] 12:30 PM - 2:30 PM: Activities in the Faculty [Location: Faculties] 2:30 PM - 3:30 PM: Program Industri: Ericsson & Talent Corp [Location: Dewan Tunku Canselor] 3:30 PM - 4:00 PM: Break Time 4:00 PM - 5:00 PM: Program Madani (KPT) [Location: Dewan Tunku Canselor] 5:30 PM - 7:00 PM: Introduction to SUKSIS & PALAPES [Location: Dewan Tunku Canselor] 7:00 PM - 8:00 PM: Break Time 8:30 PM - 9:30 PM: Session Registration 1 9:30 PM - 10:30 PM: Session Registration 2 10:30 PM - 11:30 PM: Session Registration 3"
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the activities scheduled for 2 October 2023?",
        "answer": "The activities for 2 October 2023 (Monday) include: 9:00 AM - 10:00 AM: Session with Deputy Vice-Chancellor (Academic & International) [Location: Dewan Tunku Canselor] 10:00 AM - 11:00 AM: Break Time 11:00 AM - 12:30 PM: Program Industri: Ericsson & Talent Corp [Location: Dewan Tunku Canselor] 12:30 PM - 2:30 PM: Session Registration 4 2:30 PM - 3:30 PM: Activities in the Faculty [Location: Faculties] 3:30 PM - 4:00 PM: Break Time 4:00 PM - 5:00 PM: Session with Deputy Vice-Chancellor (Student Affairs) & Student Affairs Department [Location: Dewan Tunku Canselor] 5:30 PM - 7:00 PM: Program Madani (KPT) [Location: Dewan Tunku Canselor] 7:00 PM - 8:00 PM: Break Time 8:30 PM - 9:30 PM: Student Carnival Activities [Location: Dewan Tunku Canselor] 9:30 PM - 10:30 PM: Break Time 10:30 PM - 11:30 PM: Activities in the Faculty [Location: Faculties]"
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the activities scheduled for 3 October 2023?",
        "answer": "The activities for 3 October 2023 (Tuesday) include: 9:00 AM - 10:00 AM: Session Registration 1 10:00 AM - 11:00 AM: Break Time 11:00 AM - 12:30 PM: Student Carnival Activities [Location: Dewan Tunku Canselor] 12:30 PM - 2:30 PM: Activities in the Faculty [Location: Faculties] 2:30 PM - 3:30 PM: Break Time 3:30 PM - 4:00 PM: Break Time 4:00 PM - 5:00 PM: Session with UM Clinic, Bursar, Library, Security Department, OSHREC, Counselling and Disability Empowerment Division [Location: Dewan Tunku Canselor] 5:30 PM - 7:00 PM: Activities in the Faculty [Location: Faculties] 7:00 PM - 8:00 PM: Break Time 8:30 PM - 9:30 PM: Session Registration 2 9:30 PM - 10:30 PM: Session Registration 4 10:30 PM - 11:30 PM: Activities in the Faculty [Location: Faculties]"
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the activities scheduled for 4 October 2023?",
        "answer": "The activities for 4 October 2023 (Wednesday) include: 9:00 AM - 10:00 AM: Session Registration 1 10:00 AM - 11:00 AM: Break Time 11:00 AM - 12:30 PM: Student Carnival Activities [Location: Dewan Tunku Canselor] 12:30 PM - 2:30 PM: Activities in the Faculty [Location: Faculties] 2:30 PM - 3:30 PM: Break Time 3:30 PM - 4:00 PM: Break Time 4:00 PM - 5:00 PM: Session with UM Clinic, Bursar, Library, Security Department, OSHREC, Counselling and Disability Empowerment Division [Location: Dewan Tunku Canselor] 5:30 PM - 7:00 PM: Activities in the Faculty [Location: Faculties] 7:00 PM - 8:00 PM: Break Time 8:30 PM - 9:30 PM: Session Registration 2 9:30 PM - 10:30 PM: Session Registration 4 10:30 PM - 11:30 PM: Activities in the Faculty [Location: Faculties]"
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the activities scheduled for 5 October 2023?",
        "answer": "The activities for 5 October 2023 (Thursday) include: 9:00 AM - 10:00 AM: Session Registration 1 10:00 AM - 11:00 AM: Break Time 11:00 AM - 12:30 PM: Student Carnival Activities [Location: Dewan Tunku Canselor] 12:30 PM - 2:30 PM: Activities in the Faculty [Location: Faculties] 2:30 PM - 3:30 PM: Break Time 3:30 PM - 4:00 PM: Break Time 4:00 PM - 5:00 PM: Session with UM Clinic, Bursar, Library, Security Department, OSHREC, Counselling and Disability Empowerment Division [Location: Dewan Tunku Canselor] 5:30 PM - 7:00 PM: Activities in the Faculty [Location: Faculties] 7:00 PM - 8:00 PM: Break Time 8:30 PM - 9:30 PM: Session Registration 2 9:30 PM - 10:30 PM: Session Registration 4 10:30 PM - 11:30 PM: Activities in the Faculty [Location: Faculties]"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who are the persons in charge of the registration sessions?",
        "answer": "The persons in charge of the registration sessions are: En Nasarizal Bin Nazaruddin and Pn Nur Amni Binti Mohd Supardi."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the Break Times during the Week of Welcome?",
        "answer": "Break Times are scheduled throughout each day. Specific times for breaks are provided in the detailed daily schedules."
      }
    ]
  }
